mickeymagicalyear.com 2017-11-24

# Disneyland Paris | Disneyland Paris

  * Privacy Policy

The Internet is a fun place for work and for play. However, in order for you to get the best possible use from our sites it may be necessary, in some circumstances, for you to give us personal information about yourself. This policy tells you how we collect information from you, how we protect it and how we use it. We want to help make the Internet a safe and fun experience for you, your friends and your family.

Disneylandparis.com is owned, controlled and run by Euro Disney Associés S.C.A, a company incorporated under the laws of France and having its registered offices at 1, rue de la Galmy - 77700 Chessy, France and registered with the Commercial Register of Meaux under the number 397 471 822 ("Euro Disney"). It is Euro Disney's policy that we obey and respect the law in relation to privacy and protect our guests' personal information from possible misuse. We also allow you access to your personal information so that you can amend or delete the information we have about you or ask us to do it for you.

What type of information we collect about you 

We collect two 'types' or categories of information about you:   
1\. The first type is information that personally identifies you. For example, your full name (your first name and your surname), your home (or work) address, your e-mail address, telephone number and postcode. We call this 'personally identifiable' information.   
2\. Other information you give us, by itself, is NOT personally identifiable i.e. that we cannot link to an identified person. For example, whether you are male or female, the times and dates you use are services, the country in which you live, the language you normally speak in, the number of children you have... We call this 'non-personally identifiable information' or 'aggregate' information. 

What we do with 'Aggregate' information 

Aggregate information allows us to see what 'types' of people use our site (for example, how many are girls and how many are boys). From time to time we may also run on-line surveys or questionnaires to collect your thoughts, opinions or suggestions as to how we can make our sites, products or services better for you. We may also share aggregate information with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors and third parties, so that they can better understand what type of person uses our sites.   
Remember, this information is NOT personally identifiable information from which you can be identified. 

What we do with Personally Identifiable information 

We will only collect personally identifiable information during the following:

  1. When you register to enter into our on-line competitions
  2. When you register for on-line 'clubs' that will give you special benefits like exclusive content, access to other competitions and other on-line activities
  3. When you book online
  4. When you order a brochure
  5. When you register for news and offers
  6. When you answer to surveys
  7. When you use our online assistance tools

This information is then used (i) to inform winners of a competition what prizes they have won, (ii) to fulfill your requests for products and services and notably Park tickets and / or stays at Disneyland Paris, or (iii) should you already made a booking with us, to send you information on products / services similar to those you previously purchased or (iv) depending on your prior consent, for general promotion and marketing purposes., i.e. to inform you about news, to send you special offers etc.

This personal information is ONLY used by Euro Disney and carefully selected third party service providers and is NEVER shared with other third parties, unless otherwise clearly stated at the time of collection or registration. Even then, it would only be shared when we have your permission to do so.When we post information about you on our sites, (for example, if you are a competition winner), we will never disclose personally identifiable information that could let other people know where you live or exactly who you are.

Please note that, your Personal Information will not be transferred outside the European Union unless you are informed otherwise at the time you provide your Personal Information. In any event, Personal Information will be transferred subject to the entity receiving such Personal Information provides appropriate warranties in full compliance with European regulations on data privacy.

Our Legal Obligation to Disclose Personal Information we hold about you 

Unless we have your express consent, we will not disclose, sell, rent or trade your personally identifiable information to anyone but permitted third parties, such as carefully selected third party service providers.   
We may however disclose personal information about you without your prior consent where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, get into contact with or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Euro Disney's rights or property, or anyone else who could be harmed by those activities. We may disclose member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.   
Disney may also transfer information about you if Disney acquires, or is acquired by, merged, consolidated or reorganized into or with another company. 

Disney Policies for children 

Disney encourages parents and guardians to spend time on-line with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on these sites. 

What we do with your information if you are 18 years old or over 

If you are 18 years of age or older, you may request to receive information about new content or events on our site or about other our products or services.   

Our general rules when you enter one of our on-line competitions 

All competitions that you may enter on our site have there own rules and conditions, but for any of our competitions the following general rules will apply:   
If you under age 18, you can enter our contests, but only if you have the permission of your parent or guardian. If you win a prize we will tell you either by e-mail or through the post. The prizes will be sent to your parents or guardians.   
If you enter or win a competition, and we discover that you do not have the proper permission then your entry will be ignored or invalid, as will be the offer of any prize. 

How we track your use of our site(s) ? 

In order to continually improve our web-site it is useful to know which are the popular areas on our site and how long our guests spend on them. We do this in a number of ways. These are explained below.

**• Use of IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. Web servers, the big computers that 'serve up' Web pages, automatically identify your computer by it's IP address. Euro Disney collects IP addresses for the purpose of system administration, and to create reports and to audit the use of our site. When you request pages from Disneyland Paris site, our servers or computers log the guests IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a member remains anonymous to us.

**• Use of Cookies**

**  
**Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes.

You should be aware that when you are on our site you could be directed to other sites that are belonging to the Walt Disney Company group of companies. There may have links to other sites from Disneyland Paris site that take you outside our service.   
For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a Disney search result the click may take you off a Disneyland Paris site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use or incorporate our logo our other company's or affiliates' logos as part of a joint advertising campaign. The privacy policy of the advertisers, sponsor or affiliate or partner will govern the information obtained from you on such site.   
Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information on-line-for example, via message boards or chat- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. Remember, NEVER give out personal information on a chat or bulletin board.   
We strive to protect your identity and privacy, but we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you disclose on-line, and you do so at your own risk. If you are young or inexperienced on the Internet, then ask your parents or someone else you can trust, who has some experience, about which personal information is safe to send or give on the internet. 

The importance of secure storage of your personally identifiable information is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in transmitting your information from your computer to our servers.   
Only those individuals who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any Euro Disney employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.   
Remember to close your browser window when you have finished what you've been doing; this is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or an internet café. 

Your acceptance of these terms 

By using this site, we assume that you have read this document carefully and understand and have followed its advice. If you do not agree to this policy or to the advice we give, please do not use our site. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy from time to time as necessary. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any such changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

© Disney. All rights reserved
